(Penny:)That is not true.
(Amy:)I'm still waiting
on my mini corndogs
(Amy:)from two years ago.
(Penny:)I told you,
they'll be right out.
(Amy:)Okay, so no
Bernadette.
(Penny:)Well, you saw her the
other night. Am I wrong?
(Amy:)No, I just...
(Amy:)I feel kind of uncomfortable
talking about her like this.
(Amy:)Usually when someone's being
talked about behind their back,
(Amy:)it's me and it's right
in front of my face.
I-I'm sorry. I just need
a little break from her.
(Amy:)I understand.
(Amy:)You know, there is
some research that indicates
(Amy:)that sharing negative attitudes
about a third party
(Amy:)can be a powerful bonding force
between two friends.
(Penny:)So, what are
you saying?
(Amy:)I'm saying,
in the spirit of science,
(Sheldon:)what is
that little skank's problem?
(Raj:)So, I've been trying
to come up
(Raj:)with a cute couple's nickname
for me and Emily.
(Raj:)What do you
like better--
(Raj:)Emippali...